// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "It is a process where you will separate the two different substances in a solution.",
    answer: "Separation of Mixtures",
    options: [
      "Kinetic Force",
      "Separation of Mixtures",
      "Gravitational Force",
      "London Dispersion Force"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "The separation of a mixture by passing it through a medium in order to separate it. wherein the constituents flow at different speeds, either as a solution or suspension, or as a vapour.",
    answer: "Chromatography",
    options: [
      "Chromatography",
      "Distillation",
      "Evaporation",
      "Filtration"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: " A separation technique used to separate components of a liquid combination using a heating and cooling process that takes use of variations in the volatility of each component.",
    answer: "Distillation",
    options: [
      "Chromatography",
      "Evaporation",
      "Filtration",
      "Distillation"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "It can be used to separate components of a combination containing a dissolved solid in a liquid. The liquid is evaporated, which means it is converted from a liquid to a gaseous form.",
    answer: "Evaporation",
    options: [
      "Filtration",
      "Evaporation",
      "Distillation",
      "Chromatography"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "a process for separating the components of a combination that contains an undissolved solid in a liquid.  Filtration can be done cold or hot, with gravity or with a vacuum, with the use of a funnel or with a simple glass funnel.",
    answer: "Filtration",
    options: [
      "Chromatography",
      "Distillation",
      "Evaporation",
      "Filtration"
    ]
  },
    { 
    numb: 6,
    question: "Filtration can be done with the use of?",
    answer: "Funnel",
    options: [
      "Bucket",
      "Funnel",
      "Amorphous solid",
      "Rubic's Cube"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: " When a liquid is converted to a gaseous form, it is called? ",
    answer: "Evaporation",
    options: [
      "Negative Energy",
      "Kinetic Energy",
      "Condensation",
      "Evaporation"
    ]
  },
    { 
    numb: 8,
    question: "A process where you will separate the two different substances in a solution.",
    answer: "Separation of Mixtures",
    options: [
      "Separation of product",
      "Liquid",
      "Chromatography",
      "Separation of Mixtures"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Ways to separate mixtures: evaporation, distillation, filtration and ____.",
    answer: "Chromatography",
    options: [
      "Funneling",
      "Chromatography",
      "Distillation",
      "Vapour Pressure"
    ]
  },
    { 
    numb: 10,
    question: "Thin-layer chromatography is a method of separating and identifying colored or colorable materials, particularly ___.",
    answer: "Pigments",
    options: [
      "Hypotonic",
      "Pigments",
      "alcohol",
      "Nucleus"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Liquid chromatography and gas chromatography is an example of?",
    answer: "Chromatography",
    options: [
      "Filtration",
      "evaporation",
      "Chromatography",
      "Distillation"
    ]
  },
    { 
    numb: 12,
    question: "Distillation is a separation technique that used to separate components of a liquid combination using ____ and ____",
    answer: "heating and cooling process ",
    options: [
      "Filtration Process",
      "Manipulation and deception process",
      "Stretching Process",
      "heating and cooling process"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 13,
    question: "It often requires the use of heat.",
    answer: "Evaporation",
    options: [
      "Evaporation",
      "Water",
      "Solid",
      "Gas"
    ]
  },
    { 
    numb: 14,
    question: "It is all that remains after the liquid has entirely evaporated.",
    answer: "Solid",
    options: [
      "Experiment",
      "Solid",
      "Liquid",
      "Gas"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Its' objective it is to isolate a solid from a mixture or to remove contaminants from a mixture.",
    answer: "Filtration",
    options: [
      "Distillation",
      "Filtration",
      "Chromatography",
      "mississipi"
    ]
  },
]